STOP. STOP.
Why...
did you spare my life?
Gabriel...
Where is he?
I want him dead.
What is it?
It's how he spoke to it.
It will change you.
We must make a choice.
And the Russians
have nothing to lose.
The coordinates.
Be careful.
I love you.
I will see you again.
Go with them.
He's sending the coordinates.
Our people are listening.
The roof is collapsing. Get out.
How do we kill it?
But...
...there's always a but.
Good luck.
Gabriel is down there.
Let me come with you.
His time will come.
Who will live
and who will die?
I will see you again.
I kill people.
You have to operate on me.
Close it tight.
A bandage.
A bandage please.
My clavicle... count down to my second rib.
Now...
...make an incision.
Hold this.
It's going to be OK.
Bottoms up.
Now what?
Pen... in the bag.
Pressure.
Take it apart.
Now what?
Thank you.
The blink of an eye.